<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Inno alumni portal docs</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on Inno alumni portal docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/overview/</guid><description>Overview # Website providing services for Innopolis University Alumni
Project Description # This website involves the ability to keep up with events happening in the univeristy, register for elective courses attendance and request a pass to enter university for different purposes.</description></item><item><title>Key Features</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/key_features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/key_features/</guid><description>Key Features # Customer Complaints: Customers can submit complaints directly through the telegram group mentioed on the website. Users Data Management: Admins are able to accept or deny requests from users with feedback (on reasons for example) Pass Order: Alumni users can request a pass to enter the university for different purposes from the main page of the website Elective Courses Participation Requests: Alumni users can request to attend elective courses held in the university at the time they are applying.</description></item><item><title>Stakeholders</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/stakeholders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/users/stakeholders/</guid><description> Stakeholders #</description></item><item><title>Architecture</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/architecture/</guid><description>High-Level Architecture # Include a simplified representation of the system&amp;rsquo;s architecture.</description></item><item><title>Set up</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/set_up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/set_up/</guid><description> Alumni Portal Backend # How to run # Using Python # Clone repository locally or on the server Open a shell/command line in this folder (better if it was after activating a python virtual env) Install the needed python packages pip install -r requirements.txt Run the python script: python3 main.py Using docker # Download docker locally or on the server Here the image tag name is alumni-backend you can name it as you like Also the port in docker is 8000 by default and you can map it to anything as you like docker build -t alumni-backend docker run -p 8000:8000 -d alumni-backend Inno-alumni-portal frontend # How to run or deploy # Clone repository locally or on the server Open a shell/command line in this folder To install all packages (local to the repo) using npm npm install To build the project for production npm run build To start the project on development npm start</description></item><item><title>Technologies</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/technologies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/developers/technologies/</guid><description> Frameworks and Technology # Python FastAPI Next.js Docker PostgreSQL</description></item></channel></rss>